

# Yagboyaju Mukhtar Olasunkanmi

### **Product Designer**

• Ibadan, Nigeria

I am a product designer with eight months of experience. Within these months, I have worked with an early-staged startup and as a first time entrepreneur on conceptualizing and scaling ideas through viable design thinking & interaction process.

**EXPERIENCE** 

**CEO**, **Hygeia.co** (Personal Project) February 2024 – till date

Hygeia.co is a health platform created for the sole purpose of providing in-depth health knowledge and care for individuals. It is basically a platform/ application that acts as a doctor, fitness coach and nutritionist.

- Created daily social marketing materials for the brands social platforms
- Designed users and brand side of the website UI interface
- Recreated the dashboard designs for users to publish tasks and personnels to fulfill tasks

# **Product Designer, Travrick**

May 2024 - till date

Travrick is a social media application that combines features from Instagram, Netflix, and Twitter. It is considered an evolution of both streaming platforms and social media apps with combined features from both fields.

- Designed useful assets like sitemap, low and high fidelity prototype
- Worked closely with content writers and frontend developers to ensure a uniform art direction is expressed across
- Created a two break points scalable design that fits both mobile and desktop screens

# Web devloper & Product Designer, Delta-cars

June 2024- September 2024

Delta-cars is a car-rental platform aimed at revolutionizing the car transportation system in Nigeria, a lot of Nigerians lack access to flexible car transportation which delta-cars aims to reverse. The idea is to provide flexible, efficient, ecnomic and reliable car rental services in order to provide Nigerians with maximum access to car transportation.

- Designed useful assets like sitemap, low and high fidelity prototype
- Worked closely with frontend developers to ensure a uniform art direction is expressed across
- Created a two break points scalable design that fits both mobile and desktop screens

Link: delta-car.vercel.app

(+234) 08125617036

mukhtaryagboyaju@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/mukhtaryagboyaju

#### **CREATIVE SKILLS**

User Interface Design
Interaction Design
Design system
Prototyping
User Research
Wireframing

#### **TOOLS**

Figma
Figjam
Adobe Illustrator
Canva

# **SOFT SKILLS**

Listening and speaking Problem solving Intrapersonal and empathy

# **EDUCATION**

Google UX Design
Coursera UI Design
Coursera UX Research
Coursera Wireframing &
Prototyping
February 2024

University of Ilorin Undergraduate February 2024